<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Newsletter</title>
    <link>https://www.jerkeby.se/newsletter/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Newsletter</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 26 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.jerkeby.se/newsletter/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Gadget reduction using zero-call-user-regs</title>
      <link>https://www.jerkeby.se/newsletter/posts/rop-reduction-zero-call-user-regs/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jerkeby.se/newsletter/posts/rop-reduction-zero-call-user-regs/</guid>
      <description>Introduction In my previous article history of ROP&amp;quot;, I cover the fundamental mitigation techniques and methods to circumvent them. In this article I&amp;rsquo;ll introduce you to yet another security feature in GCC and where its effective. This is a new feature and I think its important to investigate it&amp;rsquo;s potential.
Understanding the risks When I find memory corruption vulnerabilities during pentests, clients and vendors have a tendency to dispute the impact of the vulnerabilites.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>History of the ROP</title>
      <link>https://www.jerkeby.se/newsletter/posts/history-of-rop/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jerkeby.se/newsletter/posts/history-of-rop/</guid>
      <description>From 0 to eternity Hi buddies! I&amp;rsquo;m now celebrating one month down in my one man megacorp. I have decided to take some time off from client work to study and write about the future of memory corruption vulnerabilities. I want to help you understand the risks, and known controls for C programs. I think it&amp;rsquo;s easier to remember all of this in a story context. This newsletter is divided in two.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Capturing Robots With Kvicksand</title>
      <link>https://www.jerkeby.se/newsletter/posts/capturing-robots-with-kvicksand/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jerkeby.se/newsletter/posts/capturing-robots-with-kvicksand/</guid>
      <description>Last year I was doing a series ofwebinars on software fuzzing. Me andPasi from F-Secure compared methods where we tried two different techniques for fuzzing HTTP clients. Fuzzing is essentially a brute-force method for finding bugs in software. You try various inputs and see what happens. My method was based on running each fuzzer engine in a Docker instance, using a local network and a shared file system for coordination between instances.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Coffee Time</title>
      <link>https://www.jerkeby.se/newsletter/posts/coffee-time/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jerkeby.se/newsletter/posts/coffee-time/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m writing this from a cafe in Malmö. I traveled down south to work with a client and meet some old friends. On my newly won free time I have been reading up on the new issue of phrack, specifically I have had my eyes on &amp;ldquo;Twenty years of escaping the java sandbox&amp;rdquo;.
Whats noticeable about the new issue of Phrack is that a majority of the articles cover various methods for breaking out of confined execution environments rather than increasing privilege or gaining remote access.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Backdoor</title>
      <link>https://www.jerkeby.se/newsletter/posts/the-backdoor/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jerkeby.se/newsletter/posts/the-backdoor/</guid>
      <description>Today is my first day as an independent consultant and I&amp;rsquo;d like ot start off with telling you a secret. Before I open up I want to say thanks for joining my journey and give you a recap. In last weeks issue I wrote about the balance of releasing offensive research and making a positive impact. I try my best to be conscious about decisions and reduce negative impact. Because of that I&amp;rsquo;m always open to feedback on my actions so just press reply after reading this email if there is anything you think I could have done differently.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Countdown to 0day</title>
      <link>https://www.jerkeby.se/newsletter/posts/countdown-to-0day/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jerkeby.se/newsletter/posts/countdown-to-0day/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s a fuzzy feeling. That of anticipation, creativity and doing something new. When you find that one thing that no-one has done before that grant you new privileges and possibilities. Here we are, one week before the launch of my new company ready to teach and learn. Bringing 0day vulnerabilities in to the world you have to maintain a strategy to cause the least harm and yet make enough impact for vendors to fix and users to patch.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
